{
    "id": "47ddb4ab5e3a48d89d8574e94279d2f5",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I earn as much as …………………….. does.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a24284dcd275413fb587745ff8c74bce"
        },
        {
            "question": "James and ……………………… were present at the venue.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6556e61aa9954e7dac4f5c84ede4c8fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you sing as well as …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5cdab455800d4869a353ef98d84ecf9f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will you wait for Jane and …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "88d6b2e098cb46299417babdb4b0eea7"
        },
        {
            "question": "You know that as well as ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15000c1ebbc7442e96e08daaebbac61f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Between you and …………………. there are few secrets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b44b4b9d37644d4b87f31256fbe6fed1"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are not as rich as …………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2574aeb6f8b7442ba4f1402a3c71410f"
        },
        {
            "question": "John is as old as ………………………….. am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23fc5394cd0b4657ac2f6f3779aef724"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is known to my father and ………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a17d0d028b64282a8823ab82c06acd6"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as good as ……………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5d95d354310c4cb9800abd737531e9c7"
        }
    ]
}